Guide to the Daniel Goode Papers MSS.269
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Sound recordings, 210493
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings, 210495
    - Glendale Tape I, 1970s (Box 10)
    - Water Master, 1970s (Box 10)
    - Rankin Family Music (Cape Breton), 1972 (Box 10)
    - Quarter for Horns, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Glendale Tape II (Saturday Night), 1970s (Box 10)
    - Because, 1970s (Box 10)
    - Barn Gongs, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Broadcove Concert (Cape Breton) -- Reel 2, 1972 (Box 10)
    - The Thrush from Upper Dunakin, 1974 (Box 10)
    - What Does Faust Mean to You?, 1970s (Box 10)
    - Timbre: Ensemble Timbres, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Breakfast Before Plane, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Hermit Thrush Dunakin, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Clay Orch in Sound Express, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
    - Hermit Thrush (Lower Dunakin), 1977 (Box 10)
    - Glendale Tape III (Sunday Night), 1970s (Box 10)
    - Bells -- Griggstown, 1970s (Box 10)
    - Phrases of the Hermith Thrush as Duet with Another Thrush (Lower Dunakin), 1977 (Box 10)
    - Glendale Tape I, 1974 (Box 10)
    - What Does Faust Mean to You? and Avant-Garde Fest, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Improvisatie op maandag, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Fiddle Music from Cape Breton, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Circular Thoughts, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Circular Thoughts, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Phrases of the Hermit Thrush and Circular Thoughts, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Circular Thoughts (Many Takes), 1970s (Box 11)
  - Subseries B: Separated Materials, 210501
    - "Bad Alchemy N2 XXII" Booklet from Envelope with "Bad Alchemy N2 XXII" Cassette Tape, 1991; 210504 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Series V: Data disks, 210316
  Series comprises CD-Rs.
  - Subseries A: Computer media, 1972; 210500
    - Sounds Out of Silent Spaces Flyer: 1972?, ID: 269.3.0001; 210317 (Box 8, Media ID: 269.3.0001)
      Format: CD-Rs
      Annotations: Sounds out of silent spaces flyer: 1972(?); flyer designed by Philip Corner
      Note: Contains .pdf of flyer in folder X
    - Earle Brown: Photos of Perf. Dec. 1952, 1998; ID: 269.3.0002; 214638 (Box 8, Media ID: 269.3.0002)
      Format: CD-R
- Oversize Series I: Music, 210408
  This series contains oversize materials physically separated from Series I.
  - Oversize Subseries A: Scores, 1978, 1979; 210415
    - "Symphonic Thoughts", 1978; 210409 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Symphonic Thoughts" Frame Backboard, 1978; 210410 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Phrases of the Hermit Thrush", 1979; 210411 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Score (Fluxus pieces), Undated; cuid6200; 1 item one musical score (Item MSS.269.cuid6200)
      Composer: Earle Brown
      Scores.
- Oversize Series II: Printed Matter, 210418
  This series contains oversize materials physically separated from Series II.
  - Oversize Subseries A: Mailers and Announcements, 1993, undated; 210416
    - Gamelan Son of Lion Poster, 1993; 210412 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Daniel Goode Posters, undated; 210413 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Oversize Subseries C. Miscellaneous Papers
    - "All is Not Well" Signs, undated (Box 17)
    - Event Posters, undated (Box 17)
  - Oversize Subseries D: Periodicals, 1989, 2001; 210417
    - Periodicals, 1989, 2001; 210414 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Series VI. 2019 Accretion, 1954-2016; 1.75 linear feet in 1 manuscript box, 1 half manuscript box, 1 small flat box, and 2 oversize folders in shared housing
  This accretion to the Daniel Goode Papers consists of performance ephemera, subject files of music research, and Goode's philosophy papers from college. The accretion also includes a set of manuscript scrolls for Philip Corner's "Real Fantastic."
  This accretion has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - Ephemera, 1965-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Scottish Music, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Oberlin College, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Cornell University, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 6-8)
  - Pacific Sirens by Robert Erickson, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 2-Noter, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Morton Feldman, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Jackson Mac Low, 1980-2005 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Performance Programs, 1982-2016 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rutgers Avant-Garde Series, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 206 C Project, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Reviews and Announcements, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Terry Riley, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Contemporary Music Listening Sessions, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Real Fantastic Scrolls by Philip Corner, 1978 (Box 20)